(Amy:)Would have been more flattered
if you were a homosexual.
(Penny:)Guys, how 'bout
some music?
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, I wouldn't
care for that.
(Penny:)Amy?
(Amy:)No, thank you.
(Howard:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Uncomfortable
silence it is.
(Penny:)Hey, Sheldon, have you told Amy
(Penny:)what it was like for you
growing up in Texas?
(Howard:)No.
(Penny:)Well, why don't
you tell her?
(Penny:)All right.
(Sheldon:)It was hell.
(Penny:)Any follow up, Amy?
(Howard:)No.
(Penny:)I myself grew
up in Nebraska.
(Penny:)Small town
outside of Omaha.
(Penny:)Nice place, mostly family farms,
a few meth labs.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, how is this better
than uncomfortable silence?
(Penny:)I don't know.
(Penny:)I was just trying something.